Guide to the Human Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Fund (Human SERVE) records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XII: States
  - New Jersey: Schools/Students: Counties (Box 20, Folder 868)
  - New Jersey: Schools/Students, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 869)
  - New Jersey: Schools/Students, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 870)
  - New Jersey: Women (Box 20, Folder 871)
  - New Mexico, 1983-1990 (Box 20, Folder 872)
  - New Mexico, 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 873)
  - North Carolina, 1981-1987 (Box 21, Folder 874)
  - North Carolina, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 875)
  - North Carolina, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 876)
  - North Carolina, June 1992-December 1992 (Box 21, Folder 877)
  - North Carolina, 1993-May 1994 (Box 21, Folder 878)
  - North Carolina, June 1994-December 1994 (Box 21, Folder 879)
  - North Carolina, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 880)
  - North Dakota, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 881)
  - Ohio, 1977-1985 (Box 21, Folder 882)
  - Ohio, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 883)
  - Ohio, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 884)
  - Ohio, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 885)
  - Ohio, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 886)
  - Ohio, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 887)
  - Ohio, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 888)
  - Ohio, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 889)
  - Oklahoma, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 890)
  - Oklahoma, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 891)
  - Oklahoma, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 892)
  - Oklahoma, 1989-1995 (Box 21, Folder 893)
  - Oregon, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 894)
  - Oregon, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 895)
  - Oregon, January 1988-June 1988 (Box 21, Folder 896)
  - Oregon, July 1988-December 1988 (Box 21, Folder 897)
  - Oregon, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 898)
  - Oregon, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 899)
  - Oregon, 1993-1998 (Box 21, Folder 900)
  - Pennsylvania, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 901)
  - Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 902)
  - Pennsylvania, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 903)
  - Pennsylvania, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 904)
  - Pennsylvania, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 905)
  - Pennsylvania, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 906)
  - Pennsylvania, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 907)
  - Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 908)
  - Pennsylvania, January 1995-June 1995 (Box 22, Folder 909)
  - Pennsylvania, July 1995-December 1995 (Box 22, Folder 910)
  - Pennsylvania, January 1996-February 1996 (Box 22, Folder 911)
  - Pennsylvania, March 1996 (Box 22, Folder 912)
  - Pennsylvania, April 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 913)
  - Puerto Rico, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 914)
  - Rhode Island, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 915)
  - Rhode Island, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 916)
  - Rhode Island, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 917)
  - Rhode Island, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 918)
  - South Carolina, 1984-1990 (Box 22, Folder 919)
  - South Carolina, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 920)
  - South Carolina, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 921)
  - South Dakota, 1983-1991 (Box 22, Folder 922)
  - South Dakota, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 923)
  - South Dakota, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 924)
  - Tennessee, 1981-1987 (Box 22, Folder 925)
  - Tennessee, 1988-1992 (Box 22, Folder 926)
  - Tennessee, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 927)
  - Texas, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 928)
  - Texas, January 1984-July 1984 (Box 22, Folder 929)
  - Texas, August 1984-December 1984 (Box 22, Folder 930)
  - Texas, January 1985-July 1985 (Box 22, Folder 931)
  - Texas, August 1985-September 1985 (Box 22, Folder 932)
  - Texas, October 1985-December 1985 (Box 22, Folder 933)
  - Texas, January 1986-March 1986 (Box 22, Folder 934)
  - Texas, April 1986-June 1986 (Box 22, Folder 935)
  - Texas, July 1986-December 1986 (Box 22, Folder 936)
  - Texas, January 1987-March 1987 (Box 22, Folder 937)
  - Texas, April 1987-December 1987 (Box 22, Folder 938)
  - Texas, January 1988-February 1988 (Box 22, Folder 939)
  - Texas, March 1988-June 1988 (Box 22, Folder 940)
  - Texas, July 1988-December 1988 (Box 23, Folder 941)
  - Texas, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 942)
  - Texas: Curriculum, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 943)
  - Texas, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 944)
  - Texas, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 945)
  - Texas, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 946)
  - Texas, January 1994-May 1994 (Box 23, Folder 947)
  - Texas, June 1994-August 1994 (Box 23, Folder 948)
  - Texas, September 1994-December 1994 (Box 23, Folder 949)
  - Texas, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 950)
  - Texas, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 951)
  - Texas, Houston, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 952)
  - Texas, San Antonio, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 953)
  - Utah, 1985-1994 (Box 23, Folder 954)
  - Vermont, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 955)
  - Vermont, 1987-1990 (Box 23, Folder 956)
  - Vermont, 1991-1996 (Box 23, Folder 957)
  - Virginia, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 958)
  - Virginia, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 959)
  - Virginia, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 960)
  - Virginia, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 961)
  - Virginia, January 1995-July 1995 (Box 23, Folder 962)
  - Virginia, August 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 963)
  - Washington, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 964)
  - Washington, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 965)
  - Washington, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 966)
  - Washington, January 1988-June 1988 (Box 23, Folder 967)
  - Washington, July 1988-October 1988 (Box 23, Folder 968)
  - Washington, November 1988-December 1988 (Box 23, Folder 969)
  - Washington, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 970)
  - Washington, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 971)
  - Washington, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 972)
  - West Virginia, 1983-1990 (Box 23, Folder 973)
  - West Virginia, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 974)
  - Wisconsin, 1984-1996 (Box 23, Folder 975)
  - Wyoming, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 976)
- Series XIII: New York State Executive Orders
  - Campaigns, 1983-1989 (Box 23, Folder 977)
  - #43, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 978)
  - #104, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 979)
  - #104, January 1988 (Box 24, Folder 980)
  - #104, February-September 1988 (Box 24, Folder 981)
  - #104: Monitoring Surveys (Box 24, Folder 982)
  - #136, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 983)
  - #136: Implementation, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 984)
  - #136: Monitoring Implementation, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 985)
- Series XIV: New York State Legislation
  - Chronology, 1983-1992 (Box 24, Folder 986)
  - Grassroots, 1984-1988 (Box 24, Folder 987)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 988)
  - Election Day Registration, 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 989)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 990)
  - Grassroots, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 991)
  - Election Reform Law, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 992)
  - Chapter 79, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 993)
  - Chapter 29: Monitoring Survey (Box 24, Folder 994)
- Series XV: New York State Implementation
  - Board of Elections, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 995)
  - Board of Elections, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 996)
  - Board of Elections, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 997)
  - NVRA, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 998)
  - Ad Hoc Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 999)
  - Ad Hoc Task Force: Final Report, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1000)
  - Board of Elections: Subcommittee Report, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1001)
  - NVRA, January-August 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1002)
  - NVRA, September- December 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1003)
  - NVRA, September-December, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1004)
  - Board of Elections, January 1995-April 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1005)
  - Board of Elections, May 1995-October 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1006)
  - Board of Elections, November-December 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1007)
  - Board of Elections, January 1996-February 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1008)
  - Board of Elections, March 1996-December 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1009)
  - Board of Elections Report, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1010)
  - Nonprofits, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1011)
  - Board of Elections, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 1012)
  - Agency Based Training Manual, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1013)
  - Amended Forms (Box 25, Folder 1014)
- Series XVI: New York State Subjects
  - Chronology of Developments City & State, 1986-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1015)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1016)
  - Coalition for Effective Government, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1017)
  - Franking, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1018)
  - Voter Fraud, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1019)
  - Hospitals, 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1020)
  - Press Lists, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1021)
  - Purge (Box 25, Folder 1022)
  - SUNY, 1989-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1023)
  - Letters of Support, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1024)
  - Take Back Democracy Campaign, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1025)
  - 26th Amendment Coalition, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1026)
  - Voting Machines, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1027)
- Series XVII: New York City Early Years
  - Board of Elections, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1028)
  - Board of Elections Reform, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 1029)
  - Board of Elections, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1030)
  - Board of Elections, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1031)
  - Board of Elections, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 1032)
  - Executive Order #101, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1033)
  - Executive Order #101, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1034)
  - Mail-In Voter Registration Drive, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1035)
  - Voter Assistance Program, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1036)
  - Voter Assistance Program Monitoring, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1037)
  - Charter Revisions, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1038)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 1039)
- Series XVIII: New York City Voter Assistance Ccommission
  - 1040, 1988 (Box 25)
  - 1041, 1989 (Box 25)
  - 1042, January 1990-March 1990 (Box 25)
  - 1043, June 1990-December 1990 (Box 25)
  - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1044)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1045)
  - Guide for Agencies, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1046)
  - 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1047)
  - Implementation, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 1048)
- Series XIX: New York City NVRA Implementation
  - HRA Pilot Program, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1049)
  - Government Agency Survey (Box 26, Folder 1050)
  - Community Service Society, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1051)
  - Karpatkin Letters, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1052)
  - Board of Education, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1053)
  - Public Advocate (Box 26, Folder 1054)
  - Board of Elections, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1055)
  - Labor: AFL-CIO, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1056)
  - Labor Poor Voter Registration in NYC, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1057)
  - City University of New York, 1995-February 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1058)
  - 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1059)
  - Homeless Services, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1060)
  - Summary, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 1061)
  - Intro #450 NYC Pro-Voter Act, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 1062)
- Series XX: New York City Nonprofits
  - Private Agency Campaigns, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 1063)
  - Private Agency Campaigns, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1064)
  - Private Agency Campaigns "Countdown '88", 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1065)
  - Foundation Training, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1066)
  - 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1067)
  - SERVE Publications, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 1068)
  - January 1995-July 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1069)
  - August 1995-September 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1070)
  - October 1995-December 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1071)
  - 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1072)
  - 1995-1996 (no dates) (Box 26, Folder 1073)
- Series XXI: New York City Subjects
  - Poll Monitoring, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1074)
  - Poll Monitoring, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1075)
  - Poll Monitoring, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1076)
  - Poll Monitoring, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1077)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of NY, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 1078)
  - Center for Law and Social Justice, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1079)
  - City University of New York, 1983-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1080)
  - City University of New York - NVRA Compliance Survey, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 1081)
  - Con Edison, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1082)
  - Correspondence with David Dinkins, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1083)
  - Department of Employment, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1084)
  - Elections Projects, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1085)
  - High Schools November, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1086)
  - Homeless, 1984-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1087)
  - Hospitals, 1983-1996 (Box 27, Folder 1088)
  - Housing Authority, 1982-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1089)
  - Human Resources Administration, February 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1090)
  - Correspondence with Edward Koch, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1091)
  - Mayor Race, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1092)
  - National Association of Social Workers, 1983-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1093)
  - United Way, 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1094)
  - Voter Purge Press (Box 27, Folder 1095)
- Series XXII: New York Legal
  - Nonvoting Purge, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1096)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, March 1990-May 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1097)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, July 1990-September 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1098)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, October 1990-December 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1099)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, January 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1100)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, February 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1101)
  - 100%Vote et al. v. NYS Board of Elections/Tom Wallace, March 1991-March 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1102)
  - Executive Order #136 Implementation, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1103)
  - National Congress for Puerto Rican Rights v. John Sweeney, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 1104)
  - Community Service Society Lawsuit, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1105)
  - Community Service Society Lawsuit 90 Day Notices and Responses, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1106)
  - Disabled In Action v. New York City Human Resources Administration, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1107)
  - Election Law, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1108)
  - NY State Assembly Election Law Committee Testimony (Box 27, Folder 1109)
  - NYS Assembly Testimony Motor Vehicle Registration Program, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1110)
  - Council of New York Law Associates, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1111)
  - United States of America v. New York State, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1112)
- Series XXIII: Pre-NVRA State by State
  - State Chronology of Developments, 1975-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1113)
  - Human SERVE Multi-state Trip: Arizona, Colorado, Michigan, Minnesota, Nevada (Box 27, Folder 1114)
  - Multi-State Legislative Updates/Reports, 1984-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1115)
  - Multi-State Legislative Updates/Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1116)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions National (Box 27, Folder 1117)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions, Alabama-California (Box 27, Folder 1118)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions, Colorado-Maine (Box 27, Folder 1119)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions, Maryland-Nevada (Box 28, Folder 1120)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions, New Jersey-Oregon (Box 28, Folder 1121)
  - Legislation/Executive Orders/Resolutions, Pennsylvania-West Virginia (Box 28, Folder 1122)
  - Voter Registration Forms (Box 28, Folder 1123)
- Series XXIV: D.C. Office
  - Agency Based Models (Box 28, Folder 1124)
  - Agency Based Registrar Programs (Box 28, Folder 1125)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 28, Folder 1126)
  - Arizona (Box 28, Folder 1127)
  - California (Box 28, Folder 1128)
  - Citizens Commission on Civil Rights (Box 28, Folder 1129)
  - Coalition List - Outreach Letters (Box 28, Folder 1130)
  - Commission on National Elections (Box 28, Folder 1131)
  - Committee Lists/Information (Box 28, Folder 1132)
  - Common Cause (Box 28, Folder 1133)
  - Council on Foundations (Box 28, Folder 1134)
  - Alan Cranston (Box 28, Folder 1135)
  - Democratic National Committee (Box 28, Folder 1136)
  - Disabled But Able To Vote (Box 28, Folder 1137)
  - Documents for Distribution (Box 28, Folder 1138)
  - Election Day Registration (Box 28, Folder 1139)
  - Election Fraud Report (Box 28, Folder 1140)
  - Federal Elections Commission (Box 28, Folder 1141)
  - Fraud Issue (Information, Statistics, etc.) (Box 28, Folder 1142)
  - Human SERVE Budget (Box 28, Folder 1143)
  - Human SERVE Monthly Report (Box 28, Folder 1144)
  - Human SERVE - National Municipal League Model System (Box 28, Folder 1145)
  - Human SERVE Political (Box 28, Folder 1146)
  - Human SERVE State Activity and State Staff (Box 28, Folder 1147)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (Box 28, Folder 1148)
  - Linda/Richard/Requests, etc. (Box 28, Folder 1149)
  - Lobby Report (Box 28, Folder 1150)
  - Mail-In Information (Box 28, Folder 1151)
  - Meetings/Strategies/Letters (Box 28, Folder 1152)
  - Minnesota (Box 28, Folder 1153)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1154)
  - National Conference of Black Mayors (Box 28, Folder 1155)
  - National Voter Registration Network Meetings (Box 28, Folder 1156)
  - Newsletters with Voter Registration Message (Box 28, Folder 1157)
  - Originals (Box 28, Folder 1158)
  - Outreach, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1159)
  - Outreach to National Associations of Public Officials (Box 28, Folder 1160)
  - No file (Box 28, Folder 1161)
  - Overseas Voter Assistance Act (Box 28, Folder 1162)
  - Party Platforms (Box 28, Folder 1163)
  - People For The American Way (Box 28, Folder 1164)
  - Political (Box 28, Folder 1165)
  - Podesta (Box 28, Folder 1166)
  - Polls (Box 28, Folder 1167)
  - Progressive Constituency Network (Box 28, Folder 1168)
  - Republican National Committee (Box 28, Folder 1169)
  - Speeches (Box 28, Folder 1170)
  - Strategy, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1171)
  - Strategy, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1172)
  - Student Voter Registration Information/Problems (Box 28, Folder 1173)
  - Texas (Box 28, Folder 1174)
  - Uniform Poll Closing (Box 28, Folder 1175)
  - Voter Turnout in California (Hagen & Wolfinger), 1974-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1176)
  - Voting Statistics (Box 28, Folder 1177)
  - Washington Alert (Box 28, Folder 1178)
  - Women's Vote Statistics (Box 28, Folder 1179)
  - Youth (Box 28, Folder 1180)
- Series XXV: Federal Legislation
  - Senate Hearings, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1181)
  - Senate: Congressional Record, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1182)
  - Senate: Advocacy/Grassroots, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1183)
  - Senate: Planning a Universal Voter Registration Act with Cranston, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1184)
  - Senate: Discussion Drafts Universal Voter Registration Act, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1185)
  - Senate - S 1888, Cranston, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1186)
  - Senate - S 1837 Election Fraud Prevention Act, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1187)
  - Senate - S 2061, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1188)
  - Senate - S 2061 Rules Committee Hearing, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1189)
  - Senate: Grassroots, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1190)
  - Senate - S 675, Cranston/Kennedy, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1191)
  - Senate: Grassroots, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1192)
  - Senate: Discussion Drafts Senator Cranston, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1193)
  - Senate: Rules Committee Hearing, Ford, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1194)
  - Senate - S 874 Amendments, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1195)
  - Senate - S 874 Grassroots, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1196)
  - Senate - S 874 Report, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1197)
  - Senate - S 874 Administration Opposition, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1198)
  - Senate: Congressional Record, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1199)
  - Senate - S 874 Legislation, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1200)
  - Senate - S 874 Amendments, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1201)
  - Senate - S 874 Alternative, Dole/Stevens, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1202)
  - Senate: Grassroots Opposition, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1203)
  - Senate - S 874 Vote, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1204)
  - Senate - S 874 Grassroots, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1205)
  - Senate - S 874 Grassroots, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1206)
  - Senate - S 250, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1207)
  - Senate - S 250 Legislation, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1208)
  - Senate - S 250 Rules Committee Hearings, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1209)
  - Senate: Suggested Language, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1210)
  - Senate - S 250 Press Conference, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1211)
  - Senate - S 250 Congressional Record, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1212)
  - Senate - S 250 Grassroots, January 1991-May 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1213)
  - Senate - S 250 Grassroots, June 1991-December 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1214)
  - Senate - S 250 Amendments, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1215)
  - Senate - S 250 Report, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1216)
  - Senate - S 250 Hearing, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1217)
  - Senate - S 250 Vote, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1218)
  - Senate - S 921 Legislation, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1219)
  - Senate - S 874 Opposition, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1220)
  - Senate - S 250 Administration Opposition, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1221)
  - Senate - S 250 Grassroots, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1222)
  - Senate - S 250 Vote, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1223)
  - Senate - S 250 Amendments, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1224)
  - Senate - S 2, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1225)
  - Senate - S 250 Congressional Record, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1226)
  - Senate - S 250 Legislative Report, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1227)
  - Senate: Votes, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1228)
  - Senate: Grassroots/Analysis/Amendments, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1229)
  - Senate - S 2, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1230)
  - Senate - S 2 Grassroots, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1231)
  - Senate: Congressional Record, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1232)
  - Senate - S 460, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1233)
  - Senate - S 460 Grassroots, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1234)
  - Senate - S 460 Report, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1235)
  - Senate: Opposition, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1236)
  - House - HR 4367, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1237)
  - House - HR 1250, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1238)
  - House - Barriers Hearing, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1239)
  - House - HR 1668, HR 2216, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1240)
  - House: Grassroots, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1241)
  - House - HR 3086 Legislation, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1242)
  - House: Hearing, July 12, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1243)
  - House - HR 1668, HR 2216 Hearing, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1244)
  - House - HR 1668, HR 2216 Legislation, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1245)
  - House - HRES 334 Resolution, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1246)
  - House - HR 1453, HR 1454, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1247)
  - House - HR 1453, HR 1454 Grassroots, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1248)
  - House - HRES 334 Grassroots, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1249)
  - House: Congressman Frank, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1250)
  - House - HR 1668, HR 2216 Amendments, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1251)
  - House - HR 1668, HR 2216 Grassroots, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1252)
  - House, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1253)
  - House - HR 2750, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1254)
  - House - HR 2750 Legislation, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1255)
  - House - HR 3666 Conyers, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1256)
  - House - HR 3023 Voter Participation Act, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1257)
  - House - HR 2750 Amendments, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1258)
  - House: Grassroots, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1259)
  - House - HR 3950 Congressional Record and Hearings, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1260)
  - House - HR 2750 Levine Bill, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1261)
  - House: Swift, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1262)
  - House: Universal Voter Registration Act, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1263)
  - House: Congressional Record, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1264)
  - House - HR 2190 Legislation, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1265)
  - House - HR 15, HR 17 Legislation and Testimony, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1266)
  - House - HR 2190 Amendments, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1267)
  - House - HR 2190 Suggested House Report Language, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1268)
  - House - HR 2190 Report, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1269)
  - House: Grassroots, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1270)
  - House - HR 2190 Supporting Material, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1271)
  - House: Opposition, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1272)
  - House - HR 2190 - Legislation, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1273)
  - House - HR 2190 Fragile Republican Support, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1274)
  - House - HR 2190 Vote, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1275)
  - House - HR 2190 Congressional Record, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1276)
  - House - HR 2190 Report, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1277)
  - House - HR 2190 Grassroots, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1278)
  - House - HR 47 Legislation, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1279)
  - House: Congressional Record, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1280)
  - House: Grassroots, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1281)
  - House - HR 2190, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1282)
  - House - S 250 Congressional Record, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1283)
  - House - S 250 Vote, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1284)
  - House: Grassroots, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1285)